Ehsas Elias Ahmed Al azazy

Sana'a, Al Qadesia (Next to Al-Qadesia School)

Phone: +967 777 610 960

E-mail: ehsas.1998000@gmail.com

Profile

A Website Developer, with two years' experience, in website design, web development. Very capable to design and develop websites by using many techniques (Joomla Framework ,Wordpress Framework ,Laravel and Pure coding "HTML , CSS ,JS"). Also capable to learn new technologies in record time.

UX UI Designer with four years' experience, by using Adobe XD or Adobe Figma. I have a creative sense by choosing colors ,shapes and suitable identity.

Education

Higher Diploma. (2022/01- 2022/08)

Rowad Foundation

Web Development Bootcamp

Bachelors (2018-2021)

Computer Faculty – Sana'a University

Information Technology

High Diploma (2017-2018)

IYLY Institute

he Higher Technical Diploma Degree (3 years) in Internet technology program with grad (Very Good) and my rank was the third.

Experiences:

ProSite Yemen for IT Salutations Company (2021 –Present)

Web Developer, **Technical Problem Solver and reporter**

Responsible for designing and developing websites according to customers' needs using joomla CMS or pure coding. Solve technical problems for employees and especially for customers (setting up emails on all devices .. laptops , phones or iPhones). Also writing reports internally and externally for other companies).

Trainer

Training university students every year (website development training).

Web developer and UI UX designer (2019 – 2020)

Temmam Company

Develop websites using pure coding and as a UX UI designer design prototyping for websites using Adobe XD.

Training Courses:

- Certificate form E campus in Communication for Development(C4D).
- Certificate form E campus in The Backway Theatre Self- Guided.
- Certificate form E campus in Psychosocial Support for Migrants.
- Certificate form UNDSS in BSAFE.
- Certificate from Alison website in IT project manager.
- Certificate from Ola Al-maged institute in Band aid.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in job search strategies.
- Certificate from Forsa platform in the art of debate.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in Band aid.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in principles of human resource management.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in child mental health.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in introduction to entrepreneurship.
- Certificate from Edrak platform in work-life balance.
- Certificate from Edrak platform leadership skills.
- Certificate from Forsa platform in setting goals and making decisions.

PREVIOUS PROJECTS

- http://hkdev.org/
- https://squaredesign-ye.com/index.php/en/
- http://felixgarden.com/index.php/en/
- https://ablass-trading.com/index.php/en/

- http://jacmotoryemen.com/
- http://smartnet-yemen.com/newweb/
- https://github.com/EhsasElias/CAC_project.git
- https://ehsaselias.github.io/myCV/
- https://ehsaselias.github.io/apex-en/
- https://ehsaselias.github.io/
- https://ehsaselias.github.io/coffee/

also see my github account

https://github.com/EhsasElias

Languages

- Arabic native language
- English Excellent

References

ProSite company
Mr. Mohamed Al-rimi
The Executive Officer

Tel: +967 777 700 702

E-mail: alraimi@prositeyemen.com

Rowad Foundation

Ms. Eman Al-Maktari

The Coordinator of Rowad Foundation

Tel: +967 771 770 313 E-mail: info@rowad.org

Coding Academy

Mr. Haitham Al-Maqtari Former Project Coordinator Tel: +967 777 112 860

 $\pmb{\mathsf{E}\text{-}\mathsf{mail}: \underline{\mathsf{haitham.almaqtari@gmail.com}}}$

Documents

Available upon request.